Looks like there are some good ones around here.
Yeah.
Tsuwabuki-kun, you sure did something quite drastic.
You two gave Yaeno-kun that mark,
the mark of a friend who will protect the secret.
That mark can be given to only one person, you know.
If it happens again...
Sumomo, how's this look?
It looks really good, Nako-chan.
Yep, just keep on going like that, you two.
But compared to that...
You must have never done this before, right Tsuwabuki-kun?
Yeah...
Akihime-san, please teach him how.
Eh?!
I think you can just show him the step-by-step method.
Okay!
You do this...
then this.
Then this... and then like this... and...
And here! It's done!
Ah, that looks good.
This will be this year's main decoration.
We'll name it the Wishing Star!
Wishing Star?
On July 7th, if you make a wish to this golden Wishing Star, your wish will definitely come true.
It's decided. It'll be that.
Okay!
The sun is setting...
Alright...
Is the star drop going to fall down today too?
Yeah...
You have a smile on your face...
Eh? Yeah!
I've been thinking...
What should I wish for?
Something like, "I wish to be a kinder person," or...
"I wish to have more courage."
Or even something like, "I wish to have bigger breasts."
Just kidding.
I hope tomorrow will be sunny.
Since it will be Tanabata.
It's shining!
It's here, the star drop!
Let's go, Yuki-chan!
It went into the planetarium.
Err, are we able to get inside that building?
I don't see any opening.
But we need to do something and get in.
What is it?
Umm... 'puro'... 'gu'...
and also 'ridia'.
Puro Guridia!
T-This is...
...a way in, right?
Sumomo!
It's so dark, Yuki-chan.
The two drops before this were shining.
Are you alright, Sumomo?
How about we just give up for today?
I'm alright since I'm with you, Yuki-chan.
Maybe...
Well, this is for Yuki-chan's sake after all.
I'll do my best.
Sumomo...
Yuki-chan, look at that!
The star drop!
Alright, I'll try to catch it, Yuki-chan.
Puruvu Ra-
What kind of clothes are those?
And you call yourself a Stellar Spinear?
W-Who the hell are you?!
Nice to meet you, Prima Plam.
What? Prima...
...Plam?
I am the Saint Aspalas' Stellar Spinear, Prima Aspalas!
Prima... Aspalas?
Wow,
that's so cool!
Don't joke with me!
We are enemies, you know?
Rivals in gathering the star drops!
She said enemy, do you know her?
Nope.
Is that doll your servant?
Is it even competent?
Di Pieroto.
Huh?!
Yuki-chan!
What a strange little...
Yuki-chan...!
Sumomo!
Give me back Yuki-chan!
Are you alright, Yuki-chan?
Y-Yeah.
Hey, what was that for?
Are you making fun of me?
Umm...
What you said about Prima...
It's Prima Plam!
Is that...
really me?
You have the Ladle and your servant...
There is no way I'm wrong!
Ruuche Ruvi Avis!
Amazing!
Puruvi Radius!
Amazing...
She captured the star drop!
Congratulations...
...Miss.
This will be the third star drop.
Third?
The dog talked!
You're able to do so too, right?
And you're a doll on top of that.
Arthur, bring that here.
Here you are.
No, not the lunch box!
I am really sorry.
Here it is.
What do I need a mop for? No!
Well then, this one.
No, that's wrong! Wrong!
Sorry, sorry!
What are you doing?! I mean that, that thing! Don't you know?
Umm...
I'm really sorry! How about this?
These two...
That's right, it's this one.
Bring that to her.
This book looks similar to Yuki-chan's book.
Open the pages please.
Don't tell me your magical power is only that much?
You don't have to be so mean!
Being mean? You must be kidding!
Listen, this is a fight, you know.
A fight?
That's right. I want a fair fight in gathering the star drops...
with someone whose power corresponds to mine.
But since you can't even open my Recipe,
that means your level is much lower compared to mine.
You... Are you really the Prima Plam?
Umm...
Even if you don't know about it...
...you are still destined to fight with me.
Improve on your skills.
If you want to gather the star drops, that is.
You won't be getting any of the star drops from me!
Sumomo...
Wait!
Sumomo?
What happened?
If you feel sick, how about letting me handle giving out the bamboo decorations at the park?
I-I'm alright, Nako-chan.
Look, I'm healthy.
I'm alright, really.
I can hand out the bamboo decorations.
Sumomo...
Akihime...
Cheer up.
I'm sorry, Yuki-chan.
I wasn't able to catch the star drop...
Don't worry, there is always next time.
But...
Sorry...
Akihime...
In any case, we have to stop that other girl.
I see...
Another Stellar Spinear appeared.
Stop deploring and explain about it.
But this doesn't always mean it's bad news. Maybe...
Maybe...?
For now, I can only say 'maybe'.
What's with that answer?
It's not fair for Akihime.
Even last night she was...
I see. So Akihime-san did...
W-What?
Nothing at all.
Anyway, we have to go to the park today, right?
Here you go.
Thank you, Onee-chan.
This decoration here is called the Wishing Star.
Wishing Star?
That's right. If you make a wish to this star,
your wish will definitely come true.
Thank you!
Well then, I'm going to help walk these kids home.
Thank you, Onee-chan!
Bye bye.
I hope your wish comes true.
Akihime...
I have to cheer up!
From now on I will keep doing my best for Yuki-chan's sake.
For Yuki-chan's sake!
Akihime.
Tsuwabuki-kun.
Looks like you guys are done.
I hurried here from Kisaragi-sensei's room.
Umm, did you hear everything?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Umm...
A-Are you alright?
Because today, Akihime was different than usual.
Umm...
T-Thank you.
Umm I... I was just feeling kind of down.
A lot of things happened.
I see.
But tonight will be Tanabata, so...
When I think about the people who will make their wishes to the Wishing Star,
I feel better.
Is that strange?
No.
That's right, we need to clean up.
You know what?
Maybe I'm being nosy, but...
Doing something for someone else's sake or something like that...
You shouldn't have to worry about those things so much.
Because doing that will make you suffer, Akihime.
Right?
Even for that person called Yuki-chan...
...he wouldn't be happy seeing you suffer.
What should I do?
What should I do so Yuki-chan will be happy?
I can't say it any better, but...
Just be yourself. I think that is enough.
Maybe...
Sumomo-chan, welcome back.
I'm home, Dad.
Perfect timing.
I forgot something important at work.
So can I leave you to watch the house?
No problem.
Thanks.
I'll come home as soon as I can, but I'll call if I'm going to be late.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I prepared dinner, but...
if it's a problem, you can eat leftover curry in the refrigerator.
Got it!
Well then, please.
See ya later!
Watching the house, huh?
Alright!
Good for you, Sumomo.
We can somehow see the Milky Way.
The kids who got the bamboo decorations must be happy too.
That's right.
Sumomo?
Hey, Yuki-chan.
Umm, actually I...
was thinking a lot today.
From now on, that girl from yesterday will probably...
...take all of the star drops.
I don't know...
I probably won't be...
any use to Yuki-chan anymore.
That's what I thought about.
That's not true!
That's why...
I searched for what I could do.
Something that even I can do, for Yuki-chan's sake.
I will always be there with a smile...
Because that is the only thing I can do.
Look!
Eh...?
I'm... sorry...
I... can't seem to smile...
Sumomo...
Please...
Star-sama, please let me smile.
Sumomo...
Sumomo, Sumomo!
Open your eyes, slowly.
Yuki-chan, this is...?
Sumomo, your wishes will come true!
Yuki-chan!
Yuki-chan, Yuki-chan!
Thank you, Yuki-chan!
Yuki-chan.
That's right.
I was thinking of a present for you.
A present?
Last night the spell by Aspalas-san was really beautiful, so...
I thought I could see it again with Yuki-chan.
That's why...
I'll try my best.
Please, golden Wishing Star...
I want to show this to Yuki-chan!
Ruuche Ruvi Avis!
I did it!
You did it, Sumomo!
Yuki-chan!
That's amazing, Sumomo!
Thanks to you, Yuki-chan.
Thank you,
Yuki-chan.
Thank you...
...Tsuwabuki-kun.
This can't be...
What did you say?!
She mastered the "Sakuya Shirimoshinakata" skill in one night?
Yes, Miss.
It looked so beautiful, I couldn't help but stare at it.
I never asked your opinion!
Y-Yes!
Please forgive me!
Just as I thought, that girl is...
The day after the unforgettable Tanabata evening...
Alright everyone.
Be quiet please.
Just for today I will be your homeroom teacher.
First off, an introduction of a new transfer student.
Transferring at this time?
A beautiful girl with glasses!
A very high grade!
Hey boys! Don't stand up!
I'm Yuuki Nona.
That was the dawn of the troubles ahead.
It's here, it's here!
What is?
The summer is!
Hey, summer boy!
It's summer! It's the pool! It's swimming!
Speaking of swimming, that's Tsuwabuki-kun, right?
He's a completely different person once in the water.
I want to be consoled too.
Just like Sumomo-chan?